Guide to the Rawley family papers, 1822-1953.
Rawley family papers, 1822-1953.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Rawley family papers, 1822-1953.
937
Rawley family.
11.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, accounts, promissory notes, receipts, teachers' certificates, scrapbooks, clippings, printed matter, photographs, essays, legal papers, minutes, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, accounts of a general store, promissory notes, receipts, teachers' certificates, scrapbooks, clippings, printed matter, photographs, and other papers of a family living in Richford, Tioga County, New York.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
H. B. and B. C. Rawley owned a general store and print shop in Richford, Tioga County, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, accounts of a general store, promissory notes, receipts, teachers' certificates, scrapbooks, clippings, printed matter, photographs, and other papers of a family living in Richford, Tioga County, New York; includes diaries (1869-1929) of H. B. Rawley; correspondence (1895-1898) of B. C. Rawley; material relating to local amateur theatricals; essays and miscellaneous papers of Daniel and Hiram Rawley; legal papers (1874-1914) of the Pheylon family; local political records (1859-1914); trade papers (1897-1901) of the National United Press Association; minutes of the Society of Columbia of Richford and North Berkshire, the International Order of Good Templars, the Independent Order of Odd Fellows, the Village Improvement Society, and the Women's Missionary Society of Richford; also, a letter concerning Rockefeller genealogy.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rawley family.; Pheylon family.; Rawley, B. C.; Rawley, Daniel.; Rawley, H. B.; Rawley, Hiram.; Rockefeller, John D.(John Davison), 1839-1937.; Independent Order of Odd Fellows.; International Order of Good Templars.; National United Press International.; Society of Columbia of Richford and North Berkshire (Tioga County, N.Y.); Village Improvement Society (Richford, N.Y.); Woman's Missionary Society (Richford, N.Y.)
Subjects:
General stores--New York (State)--Tioga County.; Friendly societies--New York (State)--Tioga County.; Printing plants--New York (State)--Richford, N.Y.; Politics, practical--New York (State)--Tioga County.; Amateur plays--New York (State)--Richford.; Theaters--New York (State)--Richford.; Family--New York (State)--Richford.
Places:
Richford(N.Y.)--Social life and customs.; Richford (N.Y.)--Commerce.
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.; Scrapbooks.; Diaries.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Photographs, Richford, N.Y., people (Box 1)
- Additional [presumably items desc. in 1954-1958, 1958-1962 Reports] (Box 2)
- Books and pamphlets (Box 3)
- Photographs (Box 4)
- Family papers (Box 5)
- Clippings (Box 6)
- Trade cards, programs, broadsides (Box 7)
- Duplicate broadsides and playbills, local historical and genealogical material; see regular broadside collection (Box 8)
- Bills and misc. (Box 9)
- Bills and receipts, 1921-1923 (Box 10)
- Tax and assessment rolls, 1880-1912 (Box 11)
- Diaries and pamphlets (Box 12)
- 5 vols. General Store Sales, 1908 (Box 13)
- I.O.G.T. Richford Constitution (Box 13)
- Wagon Maker, 1868-1873 (Box 13)
- I.O.G.T. members and dues, 1870-1875 (Box 13)
- 2 Day Books (Box 13)
- 12 vols. (Box 14)
- 6 vols. (Box 15)
- 4 vols. (Box 16)
- 21 vols. (Box 17)
- Photographs - Richford & N.Y. scenes (Box 18)
- Plays (texts) (Box 19)
- Plays (texts) (Box 20)
- Plays (texts) (Box 21)
- Plays (texts) (Box 22)
- Southern Central R.R. (Box 23)
- Photographs - Richford, N.Y. scenes (Box 24)
- Supervisors bonds, highway records, elections excise, license, no license, parties, 1851-1901 (Box 25)
- School record (Box 26)
- Store records (Box 27)
- Tax and assessment rolls, 1855, 1879 (Box 28)
- 3 vols. (Box 29)